Neil V. Rosenberg bluegrass music collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Sound recordings, Digital files are located in afc2002009_dc001. Please see the AFC reference staff for access.
  - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys; dubs of Flatt and Scruggs Columbia 45s, AFC 2002/009: SR073; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side 1: 00:32:04, Side 2: 00:31:06): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Worcester, Massachusetts, November 16, 1963
        Personnel: Bill Keith, Del McCoury, Joe Stuart. Original recording by Pete Siegel. Continued on Side 2.
        - "Panhandle Country"
        - "Dark Hollow"
        - "On And On"
        - "Devil's Dream"
        - "Love's Gonna Live Here"
          Vocal by Melissa Monroe
        - "I Was Dreaming Of A Little Cabin"
        - "Muleskinner Blues"
        - "Footprints In The Snow"
        - "Blue Moon Of Kentucky"
        - "Rawhide"
        - "John Henry"
        - "I Saw The Light"
    - Side 2
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Worcester, Massachusetts, November 16, 1963
        - "What Would You Give"
          Duet with B. Lilly.
        - "Blue Ridge Mountain Blues"
        - "Y'all Come"
      - Dubs of Flatt and Scruggs Columbia 45s
        - "My Darling's Last Goodbye," 1952
          Columbia 4-21002 (ZSP 8899-1C)
        - "If I Should Wander Back Tonight," 1953
          Columbia 4-21125 (ZSP 12692-1A)
        - "I'm Gonna Sleep With One Eye Open," 1955
          Columbia 4-21412 (ZSP 35191-2D)
        - "Give Me Flowers While I'm Living," 1957
          Columbia 4-40928 (ZSP 41269-1C)
        - "Is There Room For Me," 1957
          Columbia 4-40928 (ZSP 41270-1A)
        - "Let Those Brown Eyes Smile At Me," 1957
          Columbia 4-40990 (JZSP 41992-1A)
        - "I Don't Care Any More," 1958
          Columbia 4-41244 (JZSP 43105-1C)
        - "Mama's And Daddy's Little Girl," 1958
          Columbia 4-41244 (JZSP 43107-1A)
  - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Bean Blossom, May 24, 1964, AFC 2002/009: SR074; RXH 8896; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:46:08, Side 2: 00:45:37): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Recorded at the Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Recorded by Jerry Garcia. Personnel: Benny Williams, fiddle; Jimmy Maynard, guitar; Bruce Weathers, banjo; Ken Marvin, bass.
    - Side 1
      - Afternoon show
        - Introduction by Marvin Hedrick
        - "Panhandle Country"
        - "Darling Corey"
        - "Georgia Rose"
        - "I'm One Of God's Sheep"
        - "White House Blues"
        - "Highway Of Sorrow"
        - "Blue Moon Of Kentucky"
          String breaks on the fiddle
        - "Footprints In The Snow"
        - "Molly and Tenbrooks"
        - "Bluegrass Breakdown"
          Knocks on the mandolin
        - "Uncle Pen"
        - "Muleskinner Blues"
        - "Mocking Bird"
        - "Kentucky Waltz"
        - "Rawhide"
        - "Prisoner's Song"
        - "Cripple Creek"
    - Side 2
      - Afternoon show
        - "Fire On The Mountain"
        - "Y'all Come"
      - Evening show
        - "John Henry"
        - "On And On"
        - "Wheel Hoss"
        - "Draggin' The Bow"
        - "On My Way To The Old Home"
        - "Bluegrass Breakdown"
        - "Bluegrass Special"
        - "Sally Jo"
        - "Muleskinner Blues"
        - "Goodbye Old Pal"
        - "Tennessee Waltz"
        - "I Saw The Light"
        - "I'll Meet You In Church Sunday Morning"
        - "I'm One Of God's Sheep"
        - "Grey Eagle"
        - "Y'all Come"
  - Jim and Jesse (Jesse at home; broadcast dubs), AFC 2002/009: SR075; Scott Hambly; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side 1: 00:31:32, Side 2: 00:31:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Jesse McReynolds at home, Prattville, Alabama, December 8, 1963
        - chord transitions
        - split string original
        - "Little Rock Getaway"
        - "Sailor's Hornpipe"
        - original tune
        - "Eight More Miles To Louisville"
        - "Farewell Blues"
        - "Dill Pickles Rag"
        - "Cripple Creek"
        - "San Antonio Rose"
        - unidentified tune
        - double time something [sic]
        - "Lonesome Road Blues"
        - "Billy In The Low Ground"
          - d string lead
          - a string lead
          - e string lead
      - Jim and Jesse and the Virginia Boys (Shelton, Buchanan, Sutherland): dubs, December 10, 1963
        WTVY-TV, Dothan, Alabama
        - "Christmas Time's A Coming"
        - "I Saw The Light"
        - unidentified fiddle tune
        - "I Can Read Between The Lines In Your Letter"
        - "Bending The Strings"
      - Jim and Jesse and the Virginia Boys, June 1963
        - "Childish Love"
    - Side 2
      - Jim and Jesse and the Virginia Boys, November 19, 1963
        - "Wildwood Flower"
      - Jim and Jesse and the Virginia Boys, November 26, 1963
        - "Love's Gonna Live Here"
        - "Please Talk To My Heart"
        - "Weeping Willow"
        - "Nine Pound Hammer"
        - "Mama Don't Allow"
        - "Where The Soul Of Man Never Dies"
        - "Ricketts Hornpipe"
        - "When My Blue Moon Turns To Gold Again"
      - Jim and Jesse and the Virginia Boys, November 27, 1963
        WEAR-TV, Pensacola, Florida
        - "Lonesome Road Blues"
        - "Hyrum's Hornpipe"
      - Jim and Jesse and the Virginia Boys, December 3, 1963
        - Theme
        - "Take My Ring From Your Finger"
        - "Talk Back Trembling Lips"
        - "Beer Barrel Polka"
        - "Little Paper Boy"
        - "Beverly Hillbillies Theme"
        - "Tennessee Wagoner"
  - Stan Freberg commercials; Lilly Brothers at Club 47, AFC 2002/009: SR076; Bill Keith; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side 1: 00:32:47, Side 2: 00:32:42): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Stan Freberg commercials, circa mid-1960s
        Commercials by Stan Freberg for Prince-brand spaghetti: six installments dubbed from radio station discs.
      - Lilly Brothers, with Don Stover, at Club 47, possibly June 19, 1964, Bill Keith
        Recorded at Club 47, Boston, Massachusetts. Continued on Side 2.
        - "She'll Be Coming Around The Mountain"
        - "Are You Missing Me"
        - "Wreck Of The Number Nine"
        - "Don't Forget Me Little Darlin'"
        - "Lonesome Pine Breakdown"
        - "There'll Come A Time"
        - "Rawhide"
        - "Dying Cowboy" ("Streets Of Laredo")
    - Side 2
      - Lilly Brothers, with Don Stover, at Club 47, possibly June 19, 1964, Bill Keith
        Continued from Side 1; continued on SR077.
        - "Dying Cowboy"
          Ending
        - "Cacklin' Hen"
          End of the set
        - "On My Way To The Old Home"
        - "Shackles And Chains"
        - "Orange Blossom Special"
        - "I'll Go Stepping Too"
        - "The Storms Are On The Ocean"
        - "Prisoner's Song"
        - "We Shall Meet"
  - Lilly Brothers, with Don Stover, at Club 47; Radio dubs, AFC 2002/009: SR077; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side 1: 00:26:14, Side 2: 00:26:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Lilly Brothers, with Don Stover, at Club 47, possibly June 19, 1964, Bill Keith
        Continued from SR076
        - "We Shall Meet"
        - "Rabbit In A Log"
        - "In The Pines" ("The Little Red Shoes")
        - "Clinch Mountain Backstep"
        - "St. Louis Blues"
        - "Maggie Dear"
        - "Roanoke"
      - Radio dubs, Bill Keith
        All dates are estimates, based on the first commercial release of the song.
        - "Salty Dog" - Flatt and Scruggs, circa 1952
        - "Mama's And Daddy's Little Girl" - Flatt and Scruggs, 1958
    - Side 2
      - Radio dubs, Bill Keith
        - "Leather Britches" - Flatt and Scruggs, 1963
        - "Don't Let Your Deal Go Down" - Flatt and Scruggs, 1957
        - "Will You Be Loving Another Man" - Lester Flatt and Mac Wiseman, 1971
        - "Stone Wall" - Hylo Brown, 1957
        - "Give Me Flowers While I'm Living" - Flatt and Scruggs, 1957
        - "Let Those Brown Eyes Smile At Me" - Flatt and Scruggs, 1957
        - "Don't Let Your Deal Go Down" - Flatt and Scruggs, 1957
        - "Lovesick And Sorrow" - Hylo Brown, 1955
        - "Shuckin' The Corn" - Flatt and Scruggs, 1957
        - "Is There Room For Me" - Flatt and Scruggs, 1957
        - "Roll In My Sweet Baby's Arms," undated
  - WWVA radio dubs: mainly Osborne Brothers and Red Allen, spring 1958, AFC 2002/009: SR078; Marvin Hedrick; RXI 0153; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:31:18, Side 2: 00:31:37): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    The recordings were dubbed in spring 1958. They were released in 1958 or before.
    - Side 1
      - Osborne Brothers
        - "Prisoner's Song"
          With Johnny Dacus
        - "Cripple Creek"
        - "Ashes Of Love"
          With Red Allen (lead voice, lead guitar)
        - "Paul And Silas"
        - "I'm A Stranger Here"
      - Toby Stroud
        - "Shucking The Corn"
        - "Sitting On Top Of The World"
      - Osborne Brothers, with Red Allen
        - "All The Good Times" (4/4)
        - "Is This My Destiny?"
        - "Weeping Willow"
        - "Gone Home"
        - "Mansion On The Hill"
        - "Please Come Back Little Pal"
        - "Seven Year Blues"
        - "Homestead On The Farm"
        - "Someday We'll Meet Again Sweetheart"
        - "It Hurts To Know"
      - Stanley Brothers
        - "Keep A Memory"
    - Side 2
      - Osborne Brothers, with Red Allen
        - "If You Don't, Somebody Else Will"
        - "Can You Forgive?"
      - Jimmy Martin
        - "Hit Parade Of Love"
        - "Train 45"
      - Osborne Brothers, with Red Allen
        - "Will You Be Satisfied That Way"
        - "Willow Garden"
        - "Give Mother My Crown"
        - "Hand Me Down My Walking Cane"
        - "San Antonio Rose"
        - "Send Me The Pillow That You Dream On"
        - "Once More"
        - "Call Me Once In A While"
        - "In The Middle Of Nowhere"
        - "Waltz"
        - "Reuben"
  - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys; Charlie Monroe; Monroe Brothers; Kelly Brothers at Bean Blossom; Keith with Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys on the Grand Ole Opry, AFC 2002/009: SR079; Marvin Hedrick; RXH 8897; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:31:38, Side 2: 00:31:49): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at the Grand Ole Opry, March 8, 1963
        Personnel: Bill Keith (first appearance with Bill Monroe), Kenny Baker, fiddle; Del McCoury, guitar. MC: Faron Young.
        - "Cindy"
        - "Goodbye Old Pal"
        - "Sailor's Hornpipe"
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Bean Blossom, July 1, 1956
        Recorded at the Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Roger Smith, fiddle (on twins only); Carlos Brock, guitar; Joe Stuart, banjo; Tex Watson, bass; also Bobby Hicks, fiddle; Noah Crase, banjo (only on "Lonesome Road Blues"). Continued on Side 2.
        - "Georgia Rose"
        - "Girl In The Blue Velvet Band"
        - "Footprints In The Snow"
        - "Put My Little Shoes Away"
        - "Swing Low, Sweet Chariot"
        - "Uncle Pen"
        - "Wheel Hoss"
        - "Down Yonder"
        - "Mother's Not Dead"
          Lead sung by Joe Stuart
        - "Lonesome Road Blues"
        - "Roanoke"
        - "I'm Just A Used To Be To You"
    - Side 2
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Bean Blossom, July 1, 1956
        - "Prisoner's Song"
        - "Rawhide"
      - Charlie Monroe at Bean Blossom, July 1, 1956
        Recorded at the Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Personnel: Bobby Hicks, fiddle; Joe Stuart, banjo.
        - "Don't Make Me Go To Bed"
        - "Who's Calling You Sweetheart"
        - "Willow Garden"
        - "Kentucky Bound"
        - "Good Morning To You"
        - "Find 'Em, Fool 'Em, And Leave 'Em Alone"
        - "Hopalong Peter"
      - Kelly Brothers at Bean Blossom, July 1, 1956
        - "All Over Again"
        - "Where Will You Be On That Last Great Day"
        - "Leaving Tennessee"
        - "This Wild Life"
        - "Devil's Little Angel"
      - The Monroe Brothers (Bill, Charlie, and Birch) at Bean Blossom, July 1, 1956
        - "When The Angels Carry Me Home"
        - "Just A Little Talk With Jesus"
        - "Angels Rock Me To Sleep"
  - Oberlin Hoot (Oberlin College, Oberlin, Ohio), May 3, 1958, AFC 2002/009: SR080
    - Sound recording, RXI 0154; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:30:47, Side 2: 00:31:11): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Co-op Creative Arts Festival. Recorded in the Grey Gables living room. Taped by remote live at WOBC by Pete Franklin and Al Gourevitch.
      - Side 1
        - Introduction - Bo Israel, MC
        - "Raise A Ruckus Tonight" - Little Brown Jug Band
          Personnel: Mayne Smith, harmonica; Charles Crawford, guitar; Neil Rosenberg, guitar and kazoo; Phil Specht, jug; Bo Israel, washtub bass.
        - "Pretty Polly" - Mayne Smith
        - "Brownie McGhee and Sonny Terry Blues" - Charles R. Crawford
        - "Cotton Fields" - Mayne Smith (banjo) and Neil Rosenberg (guitar)
        - "Blind Man Stood On The Way" - Neil Rosenberg
        - "Backwater Blues" - Little Brown Jug Band
        - "Red Apple Juice" - Charles Crawford (guitar, vocal), Bo Israel (banjo)
        - "The Jealous Lover" - Mayne Smith
        - "Old Tom Moore" - Neil Rosenberg
      - Side 2
        - "Oh! Freedom" - Little Brown Jug Band
        - "Mi Caballo Blanco" - Erika Sherover (guitar), Chuck Crawford (banjo)
        - "This Train" - Mayne Smith, lead
        - "Veriminin Gondolas (?)" - Sophie Healy, Erika Sherover
        - "Henry Martin" - Mayne Smith (vocal, banjo), Neil Rosenberg (guitar)
        - "Lady Isabel And The Elf Knight" - Mayne Smith
        - "Jenny Jenkins" - Erika Sherover (guitar), Charles Crawford (banjo)
        - "Four Marines" - Ricky Sherover (guitar)
        - "Take Your Fingers Off It" - Little Brown Jug Band
        - "Mama Don't Allow" - Little Brown Jug Band
    - Documentation
      - Song list and production notes for SR080, April 13, 2011, nvrms1958-05-03.txt; 1 manuscript; black and white, digital (.txt)
  - Stanley Brothers at Bean Blossom; Mac Wiseman at Bean Blossom, AFC 2002/009: SR081; Marvin Hedrick; RXH 8898; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:32:36, Side 2: 00:31:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Stanley Brothers at Bean Blossom, 1955
        Recorded at the Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Personnel: Ralph Mayo, fiddle; possible George Shuffler, bass.
        - "Dickson County Breakdown"
        - "Cacklin' Hen"
        - "Are You Waiting For Me"
        - "Don't Let Your Deal Go Down"
        - "Baby Girl"
        - "Hard Times"
        - "So Blue"
        - "Will You Be Lovin' Another Man"
          Trio, with Ralph Mayo
        - comedy routine (probably George Shuffler:"Irene"/"Hound Dog")
        - "Listen To The Mocking Bird"
        - "Those Bitter Tears"
          This probably includes Ralph Mayo
        - "Rabbit In A Log"
        - "White Dove"
        - "A Voice From On High"
        - "Orange Blossom Special"
        - "I Just Got Wise"
    - Side 2
      - Mac Wiseman at Bean Blossom, circa 1955
        Recorded at the Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Continued from SR027.
        - "Me And My Fiddle" [sung by Curtis Lee]
        - "Bluegrass Breakdown"
        - "Remembering"
        - "Little White Church"
        - waltz - Buck Graves
          Possibly "Spanish Fandango"
        - "Shucking The Corn" - Buck Graves
        - "Four Walls Around Me"
        - "If Some Folks Could Leave Us Alone"
        - "Davy Crockett"
      - Radio dubs
        Continued on Bluegrass Anthology 02.
        - "Rose Of Old Kentucky" - Bill Monroe
        - "Angel Band" - Hack Johnson
        - "Dear Old Dixie" - Hack Johnson
        - "Sunshine Special" - Hack Johnson
        - "Home Sweet Home" - Hack Johnson
        - "In Despair" - Bill Monroe with Edd Mayfield (tuned mandolin)
        - "Grey Eagle" - Hack Johnson
        - "Seven Years" - Hack Johnson
        - "Walking In Jerusalem" - Hack Johnson
  - Osborne Brothers at Bean Blossom, August 9, 1964, AFC 2002/009: SR082; RXH 8899; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:43:37, Side 2: 00:45:11): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Recorded at the Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Also playing with the Osborne Brothers: Benny Birchfield.
    - Side 1
      - Afternoon show
        - Introduction - Shorty Shehan
        - "Worried Man Blues"
        - "Take This Hammer"
        - "Fair And Tender Ladies"
        - "I Saw Your Face In The Moon"
        - "Bugle Call Rag"
        - "This Heart Of Mine Can Never Say Goodbye"
        - "I Know What It Means To Be Lonesome"
        - "Steal Away"
        - "The Cuckoo"
        - "Della Mae"
        - "Once More"
        - "Billy In The Lowground"
        - "Bluegrass Express"
        - "Ruby"
      - Evening show
        This was the last song of the evening show that begins on Side 2.
        - "Ruby"
    - Side 2
      - Evening show
        Ann Rosenberg played bass at the evening show, which ends with the last song on Side 1.
        - "Salty Dog"
        - "Let's Be Sweethearts Again"
        - "Six White Horses"
        - "Faded Love"
        - "Red Wing"
        - "Bluegrass Express"
        - "Cryin' Holy Unto The Lord"
        - "Cumberland Gap"
        - "Cripple Creek"
        - "Teardrops In My Eyes"
        - "Pain In My Heart"
        - "Malaguena"
        - "Ho Honey Ho"
        - "Give This Message To Your Heart"
        - "Lost Indian"
        - "Send Me The Pillow That You Dream On"
        - "Blues Bit"
  - Jesse McReynolds at home; Jim and Jesse broadcast dubs, AFC 2002/009: SR083; Scott Hambly; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side 1: 00:46:39, Side 2: 00:48:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Jesse McReynolds at home, Prattville, Alabama, February 16, 1964
        - "Lonesome Road Blues"
        - "I Saw The Light"
        - chord transitions
        - "Stoney Creek"
        - "Old Joe Clark"
        - "Sally Goodin"
        - "Leather Britches"
        - "Florida Blues"
        - "Indian Love Call"
        - "Boil Them Cabbage Down"
      - Jim and Jesse, WEAR-TV (Pensacola, Florida), February 1964
        - "Act Naturally"
        - "Jimmy Brown The Newsboy"
        - "Las Cassas Tennessee"
        - "I Saw The Light"
      - Jim and Jesse, WEAR-TV (Pensacola, Florida), February 26, 1964
        - "Sleepy Eyed John"
        - "Buffalo Gals"
        - "Just A Girl I Used To Know"
        - "Which One Is To Blame?"
        - "Carroll County Blues"
        - "Gone Home"
        - "Foggy Mountain Top"
      - Jim and Jesse, WTVY-TV (Dothan, Alabama), March 3, 1964
        - "I Wish You Knew"
        - "Talk Back Trembling Lips"
        - "Dear Old Dixie"
        - "You've Gotta Be My Baby"
        - "Life's Railway To Heaven"
    - Side 2
      - Jim and Jesse, WTVY-TV (Dothan, Alabama), March 3, 1964
        - "Must You Throw Dirt In My Face"
        - "Arkansas Traveler"
          Includes station breaks
      - Jim and Jesse, WEAR-TV (Pensacola, Florida), March 4, 1964
        - "Head Over Heels In Love"
        - "Florida Blues"
        - "Who'll Sing For Me"
        - "Stoney Creek"
      - Flatt and Scruggs
        - "Mail Order Bride"
          From "The Beverly Hillbillies" (TV show).
      - Jim and Jesse, WTVY-TV (Dothan, Alabama), March 10, 1964
        - "Uncle Pen"
        - "How Do You Talk To A Baby?"
        - "Orange Blossom Special"
        - "Fraulein"
        - "Wings Of A Dove"
        - "Chicken Reel"
      - Jim and Jesse, WEAR-TV (Pensacola, Florida), March 11, 1964
        - "Sittin' On Top Of The World"
      - Jim and Jesse, WEAR-TV (Pensacola, Florida), April 8, 1964
        - "Heaven"
        - "I'll Never Love Another"
        - "Down Yonder"
      - Jim and Jesse, WTVY-TV (Dothan, Alabama), April 14, 1964
        - "Blue Bonnet Lane"
        - "Good Woman's Love"
        - "Polka On A Banjo"
        - "Angel Band"
        - "More Pretty Girls Than One"
      - Jim and Jesse, WTVY-TV (Dothan, Alabama), May 1964
        Continued on SR084
        - "My Empty Arms"
  - Jim and Jesse (broadcast dubs), AFC 2002/009: SR084; Scott Hambly; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side 1: 00:46:15, Side 2: 00:37:16): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Jim and Jesse, WTVY-TV (Dothan, Alabama), May 1964
        Continued from SR083
        - "Under The Double Eagle"
        - "It's A Long, Long Way To The Top Of The World"
        - "Old Time Religion"
        - "Blackberry Blossom"
        - "Rawhide"
      - Jim and Jesse, WEAR-TV (Pensacola, Florida), May 13, 1964
        - "Pardon Me"
        - "Cotton Mill Man"
        - "I Don't Love Nobody"
        - "Mountain Dew"
        - "Rock Of Ages"
        - "Send Me The Pillow That You Dream On"
        - "Leather Britches"
        - "Grave In The Bend Of The Valley"
      - Jim and Jesse, WTVY-TV (Dothan, Alabama), June 2, 1964
        - "Nine Pound Hammer"
        - "Pike County Breakdown"
        - "I'll Be No Stranger There"
        - "East Tennessee"
      - Jim and Jesse, WEAR-TV (Pensacola, Florida), June 3, 1964
        - "Soldier's Joy"
      - Jim and Jesse, WEAR-TV (Pensacola, Florida), June 10, 1964
        - "Beer Barrel Polka"
        - "Where The Roses Never Fade"
        - unidentified song
        - "Best Dressed Beggar In Town"
        - "Don't Say Goodbye If You Love Me"
      - Jim and Jesse, WTVY-TV (Dothan, Alabama), June 16, 1964
        - "Dixie Breakdown"
        - "Precious Memories"
    - Side 2
      - Flatt and Scruggs TV show; Billy Grammer, guest star
        Monroe Fields plays mandolin with Flatt and Scruggs
        - Pet Milk ad
        - "Salty Dog Blues"
        - "Wabash Cannon Ball"
          With Billy Grammer
        - "Some Day We'll Meet Again Sweetheart"
        - "Home Sweet Home"
        - "Are You Washed In The Blood"
        - "I Saw Your Face In The Moon"
        - "Foggy Mountain Special"
        - "Is There Room For Me?"
        - "Stoney Point"
      - Grand Ole Opry, July 11, 1964
        - "Cotton Mill Man" - Jim and Jesse
        - "Old, Old House" - Bill Monroe
        - "Darlin' Corey" - Bill Monroe
        - "Shady Grove" - Flatt and Scruggs
        - "Close By" - Bill Monroe
        - "Take My Ring From Your Finger" - Jim and Jesse
  - Frank Wakefield (mandolin) and Red Allen (guitar) informal sessions 1, circa 1963-1964, AFC 2002/009: SR085; Joe Fineman (via Chuck Crawford); 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side 1: 00:33:27, Side 2: 00:33:01): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Continued on SR086.
    - Side 1
      - instrumental
      - "New Camptown Races"
      - "Well Enough Alone"
      - "'Tis Sweet To Be Remembered"
      - "Bluegrass Special" (or "Bluegrass Stomp")
      - "Turkey In The Straw"
      - "Willow Garden"
      - "Bluegrass Breakdown"
      - "I'm Blue, I'm Lonesome Too"
      - "Will You Be Satisfied That Way"
      - "Long Black Veil"
      - "Teardrops In My Eyes"
    - Side 2
      - Crying Heart Blues
      - "messing around"
        Impromptu playing
      - "Nine Pound Hammer"
      - "Green Apples"
        Instrumental
      - "I Want My Baby Out Of Jail"
      - instrumental #1
        Rendition 1
      - "Are You Afraid"
      - "Swing Low, Sweet Chariot"
      - "Wicked Path Of Sin"
      - instrumental #1
        Rendition 2
      - "Paddy On The Turnpike"
      - "Billy In The Lowground"
      - "Over The Hills To The Poorhouse"
      - instrumental #2
      - instrumental #3
      - "Merle Travis' Talking Guitar"